(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
やっほーやっほーやっほー！
Yah-ho! Yah-ho! Yah-ho!
なんなんなんのーら！
Nan-nan-nan-nora!
ルカルカ★ナイトフィーバー
作詞・作曲 SAM
Luka Luka ★ Night Fever
Lyrics/Composition: SAM
ピンキー・カラー・フルなデート
A pink-colored, full date
言葉のキャレンドル
A calendar of words
退屈そうな顔
Your bored-looking face
画面見つめる君
Looking at the screen
次元の壁越えて
Beyond the wall of dimensions
いつでも会いに行く
I'll come to see you anytime
心の準備を
Get your heart ready
ちゃんとしておいてね
And be prepared, okay?
君のこと誰よりもわかってる
I know you better than anyone else
だから私に任せて
So leave it all to me
怖がらないで
Don't be afraid
二人で踊りましょう
Let's dance together
ルナルナ★ナイトフィーバー
Luna Luna ★ Night Fever
弾けるリズムに合わせて
To the popping rhythm
嫌なこと何もかも
Forget everything bad
全部忘れて
Just forget it all
ルナルナ★ナイトフィーバー
Luna Luna ★ Night Fever
私はそこにいるから
Because I'm right there
少しでも視線を
Don't even for a moment
そらしちゃダメなのら
Take your eyes off me-nora
想ってて見れない日
On days I couldn't see you despite thinking of you
呆気にとられた日
On days I was taken aback
心で呼んでみて
Try calling me in your heart
すぐに飛んで行くわ
I'll come flying to you right away
強い子は教わらないこと
Things that strong girls aren't taught
君に教えてあげるわ
I'll teach them to you
夜の扉を
Let's open the door
二人で開きましょう
Of the night together
ルナルナ★ナイトフィーバー
Luna Luna ★ Night Fever
溢れる想いは浮遊
My overflowing feelings are floating
限りあるこの時を
This limited time
胸に刻んで
Engrave it in your heart
ルナルナ★ナイトフィーバー
Luna Luna ★ Night Fever
朝日が昇ればさよなら
Once the morning sun rises, it's goodbye
寂しそうな顔して
Don't make such
ちゃダメなのら
A lonely face-nora
君のこと誰よりもわかってる
I know you better than anyone else
だから全てをさらして
So expose everything
生まれた意味を
The meaning of being born
二人で見つけましょう
Let's find it together
ルナルナ★ナイトフィーバー
Luna Luna ★ Night Fever
高まる鼓動を感じて
Feel the quickening heartbeat
さあ、覚悟ができたら
Now, if you're prepared
この手を取って
Take this hand
ルナルナ★ナイトフィーバー
Luna Luna ★ Night Fever
輝く君が好き
I love the shining you
全力で飛び出す
Leap out with all your might
用意はいいかしら
Are you ready?
ルナルナ★ナイトフィーバー
Luna Luna ★ Night Fever
弾けるリズムに合わせて
To the popping rhythm
嫌なこと何もかも
Forget everything bad
全部忘れて
Just forget it all
ルナ　ルナ　ナイトフィーバー
Luna Luna Night Fever
私は　ここにいるから
Because I am right here
少しでも　視線を
So give me your gaze
そらしちゃ　ダメダメよ
Even if just for a bit, don't look away
うー！
Woo!
ダメダメよ
Don't look away
んなあああああ！みんなーーーー！
Nnaaaaaa! Everyone!
おんるなぁああああああ！
On-Lunaaaaaaaa!
もう、突然オートが始まったから、もうびっくりしちまったのらよ。
The auto-play started suddenly, so I was really surprised!
本番が始まるまで油断してまったりしてたのら。いひひ。
I was relaxing and let my guard down until the show started. Hehehe.
ということで、本日……
So, today...
2022年……
January 4th...
1月4日は、ルーナの活動2周年記念日なのらよー！
2022, is the 2nd anniversary of Luna's debut!
見に来てくれてありがとうなのらー！
Thank you for coming to see me!
みんなのおかげで、今日という素敵な日を迎えられたのらよ。
Thanks to everyone, I was able to welcome this wonderful day.
おる、おる、みんなおるね。
They're here, they're here, everyone's here.
うおー、ありがとう、みんな来てくれてありがとう。
Wow, thank you, thank you everyone for coming.
そうね……
Right...
まず今日、こちらのね、#姫森ルーナ2周年記念LIVE で、ツイートいっぱいしてください。
First of all, please tweet a lot today using #HimemoriLuna2ndAnniversaryLIVE.
いぇいいぇい。
Yay, yay.
で、今日……
And today...
最後にはね……
at the end...
すごい、すごーい重大発表があるのらよ。
there's a really, really major announcement.
なので最後まで見ていってねー！
So please watch until the very end!
そろそろ、最初のゲストが来るはず……
The first guest should be coming soon...
うふふふっ。
Ehehehe.
ピンポーン、ピンポーン、ピンポーン。
Ding-dong, ding-dong, ding-dong.
何の音？
What is that sound?
何、うるせ、うるせ！
What, shut up, shut up!
うるせーのら！
Shut up-nora!
ガチャガチャ、開けてー！
*Rattle rattle* Open up!
え、やば、ルーナ寝てるんじゃなーい？
Oh man, is Luna sleeping?
えー、やっぱお寝坊さんだね。
She really is a sleepyhead.
この声……ちょっと待って、ちょっと待って……
This voice... Wait a second, wait a second...
ルーナ大丈夫？
Luna, are you okay?
生きてるかー？
Are you alive?
おー、生きてる生きてる！
Oh, I'm alive, I'm alive!
やだ、どこからどこから？
Oh no, where from, where from?
どうしたの？え、何々？
What happened? Wait, what's going on?
ルーナ生きてるじゃん。
Luna's alive after all.
生きてるけど……
I'm alive, but...
寝てただけね。
She was just sleeping.
寝てなかった！起きてたし！
I wasn't sleeping! I was awake!
ハロー、機動戦士AZKiです。
Hello, I'm Mobile Suit AZKi.
アロー、ロボ子だよー。
Hello, I'm Roboco!
うわー！
Whoa!
え、何何、うちにどうしたの？
Wait, why are you at my place?
だってお菓子があるって言うから……
Because you said there would be snacks...
パーティーの招待状来たけど……
We got an invitation to the party, but...
お菓子食べ放題やん。
it's all-you-can-eat snacks!
そんなの送った覚えなのらけど……何の話ししてるのら？
I don't remember sending that... what are you talking about?
え、でもほら、ケーキもクッキーもなんか……
But look, there's cake and cookies...
タコ焼きあるけど……
and even takoyaki!
ケーキ食べたかったんだよね。
I really wanted to eat cake.
い、いいけど……
W-well, okay, but...
いただきまーす！
Let's eat!
え、マジで食うのかよ、おい、ちょっ……
Are you seriously going to eat? Hey, wait...
なんか固い。
It's kind of hard.
おい、何これ？
Hey, what is this?
夢の味。
The taste of dreams.
何何、二人とも、本当は何、何しに来てくれたの？
What is it? What did you two really come here for?
え、ただ食べに来ただけだけど……
Well, we just came here to eat...
おい！
Hey!
なんなのよ。
What's with that?
しょうがないなー。お祝いしてあげるか。
Oh well. I guess we should celebrate then.
お祝い、お祝い、お祝いしちゃうのら。
Celebrate, celebrate, we're gonna celebrate-nora!
いくよー。
Here we go.
せーの！
One, two!
ルーナ、2周年おめでとう！！
Luna, congratulations on your 2nd anniversary!!
パフパフパフ！いぇーい！
*Honk honk honk* Yay!
2歳になったかー。
So you've become 2 years old.
うわーい！
Yay!
2歳……2歳じゃねーのらけどね。
2 years old... I'm not 2 years old, though.
僕たちが出会って2歳の誕生日なんだね。
It's the 2nd birthday since we met, isn't it?
誕生日じゃねーのら、2周年だから！間違えないでほしいのらよ！
It's not a birthday, it's the 2nd anniversary! Get it right!
でっかくなったことは確かだよね。
You've definitely gotten bigger, though.
ね、確かに。
Yeah, for sure.
もう、お立ちができる。
You can even stand on the platform now.
できとるわ！前からできとったわ！
I can! I could do it before!
なんなのら！
What are you talking about!
態度も随分大きくなっちまってよー。
Your attitude has gotten quite big too.
ま、姫だからな。我、姫のら。
Well, I'm a princess after all. I'm a princess-nora.
あー、元カレだこれ、元カレだわ。
Ah, she's like an ex-boyfriend, totally.
元カレだ、態度が。
Her attitude is like an ex-boyfriend's.
でもでもでも、せっかくだから、この3人、あんぽんたん姉妹で一緒にね……
But since we're here, let's do something together as the Anpontan Sisters...
アキたんとロボ子さんにも、歌って踊ってほしいのら！
I want Aki-tan and Roboco-san to sing and dance too!
あらあら、それはおねだり上手ね。
Oh my, you're quite good at asking for things.
い、あらあら。
Yes, oh my.
歌ってくれる？
Will you sing for me?
今日は、ルーナちの言うこと全部聞いてあげる。
Today, we'll do whatever Luna-chi says.
わー！嬉しい！え、どうしようどうしよう！
Wow! I'm so happy! Oh, what should I do, what should I do!
どんどんどうしようじゃないのよお前。本話は静かにして今日。
Stop panicking. Be a little quiet today.
温かいよ。ちょっと待ってよ。
It's so heartwarming. Wait a second.
じゃ、3人で一緒に歌うのら！
Then, let's the three of us sing together!
歌うのらー！
Let's sing!
バラライカ
Balalaika
ゆらりゆらり揺れている乙女心ピンチ
Swaying, swaying, a maiden's heart is in a pinch
かなりかなりヤバいのよ 助けてダーリン フラフラリ
It's really, really bad, help me darling, I'm dizzy
何もかもが新しい世界に来ちゃったわ
I've come to a world where everything is new
たくさんのドキドキ
So many heart-poundings
乗り越えふりふらり行くぜ
I'll overcome them and keep going
バラライカ バラライカ バラライカイカ この想いは止められない
Balalaika, Balalaika, Balalaika-ika, I can't stop these feelings
もっとドットマジックパワー きらりに もうときめくな感じ
More Dot Magic Power, sparkling, such a heart-fluttering feeling
バラライカ バラライカ バラライカイカ もうドキドキ止められない
Balalaika, Balalaika, Balalaika-ika, I can't stop this pounding heart
もっとドラマチック恋 ハレルヤ 2人だけのバラライカ
A more dramatic love, Hallelujah, a Balalaika for just the two of us
すぐにすぐに近づいて 乙女心チャンス
Getting closer and closer, a maiden's heart opportunity
ハート ハート 飛び出しそう
Heart, heart, it feels like it's going to jump out
お願いダーリン ハラハラリ
Please darling, I'm on edge
あなただけを見つめてる 私にちんぷんかん
Staring only at you, I'm completely clueless
気づいてほしいのな
I want you to notice me
ときめきヤキモキ 好きよ
Heart-throbbing, feeling impatient, I love you
バラライカ バラライカ バラライカイカ の秘密を教えてよ
Tell me the secret of the Balalaika-ika
もっとオドロチック もっときらりに ヤッホー 笑顔が素敵
More surprising, more sparkling, yahoo, your smile is wonderful
バラライカ バラライカ バラライカイカ もう見せてちゃダメダメよ
Balalaika, Balalaika, Balalaika-ika, you can't show it yet
もっとロマンチック恋 シャラララ なでたいのバラライカ
A more romantic love, sha-la-la-la, I want to stroke the Balalaika
女の子はいつだって 夢見る乙女なの
Girls are always dream-filled maidens
ピュアピュアな心で
With a pure, pure heart
恋して愛して E-O-S! E-O-S!
Falling in love, being in love, E-O-S! E-O-S!
バラライカ バラライカ バラライカイカ この想いは止められない
Balalaika, Balalaika, Balalaika-ika, I can't stop these feelings
もっとドットマジックパワー きらりに もうときめくな感じ
More Dot Magic Power, sparkling, such a heart-fluttering feeling
バラライカ バラライカ バラライカイカ もうドキドキ止められない
Balalaika, Balalaika, Balalaika-ika, I can't stop this pounding heart
もっとドラマチック恋 ハレルヤ 2人だけのバラライカ
A more dramatic love, Hallelujah, a Balalaika for just the two of us
バラライカ
Balalaika
ワン、ツー、スリー、フォー！
One, two, three, four!
I want you! I want you!
I need you! I need you!
I love you! 頭の中 ガンガン鳴ってるミュージック
I love you! The music is pounding in my head
ヘビーローテーション
Heavy Rotation
ポップコーンが弾けるように
Just like popcorn popping,
「好き」という文字が踊る
the word "love" is dancing.
顔や声を想うだけで
Just by thinking of your face and voice,
居ても立ってもいられない
I can't sit still.
こんな気持ちになれるって
Being able to feel this way,
僕はついているね
I'm so lucky.
I want you! I need you! I love you!
君に会えて
Since I met you,
どんどん近づくその距離に
as that distance gets closer and closer,
MAXハイテンション
I'm at MAX high tension.
I want you! I need you! I love you!
ハートの奥
Deep in my heart,
ジャンジャンあふれる愛しさは
the overflowing affection is
ヘビーローテーション
on heavy rotation.
人は誰も
Everyone,
一生のうち
in their lifetime,
何回愛せるのだろう
how many times can they love?
たった一度
If I can have
忘れられない
one unforgettable
恋ができたら満足さ
love, I'll be satisfied.
そんなトキメキを感じて
Feeling that kind of excitement,
花は開くのかな
I wonder if the flowers will bloom.
I feel you! I touch you! I hold you!
夢の中で
Inside my dream,
だんだん大きくなって行く
growing bigger and bigger
僕のイマジネーション
is my imagination.
I feel you! I touch you! I hold you!
この想いを
Because I want to
ビンビン伝えて欲しいから
strongly convey these feelings,
ヘビーローテーション
on heavy rotation.
いつも聴いてた Favorite song
That favorite song I always listened to,
あの曲のように
just like that song,
ずっと繰り返し
repeating forever,
24時間
24 hours a day,
君だけ
it's just you
リクエスト中
under request.
I want you! I need you! I love you!
君に会えて
Since I met you,
どんどん近づくその距離に
as that distance gets closer and closer,
MAXハイテンション
I'm at MAX high tension.
I want you! I need you! I love you!
ハートの奥
Deep in my heart,
ジャンジャンあふれる愛しさは
the overflowing affection is
ヘビーローテーション
on heavy rotation.
(荒い息遣い)
(Heavily panting)
ルナたん大丈夫なのら？
Luna-tan, are you okay-nora?
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
ちょっとだけ... つかれたのらけど...
I'm okay... but just a little bit... (panting)
大丈夫？
Are you okay?
お水、お水どこなのら
Water, water, where is it-nora?
お水飲もっか、お水飲もっと
Let's drink some water, drink some water.
二人とも元気なのらね
You two are so energetic-norane.
アキちゃんまだまだ全然いけちゃうのら！
Aki-chan is still, still completely fine-nora!
そのいけるステップとか、なんかできちゃう系なのら？
Wait, can you do that light step or something like that-nora?
しょうがないのら、アキちゃんこんな感じとか？
Well, since you insist-nora, how about something like this?
え、見せてくれるのら？
Eh, you're going to show us-nora?
やーい！
Yay!
元気すぎるのら！
You're too energetic-nora!
軽やかすぎるのらけど！
But you're so light on your feet-nora!
何そのフットワーク！
What's with that footwork!
ロボ子も、このステップとかできるのら？
Roboco, can you do this step too-nora?
ロボ子もできるけど... や、やるの？
Roboco can do it too, but... are we doing this?
え、ちょっとやってみて。
Eh, try doing it for a bit.
もう一回お手本見せて。
Show us the example one more time.
もう一回見せたい。
I want to show it one more time.
いくよ！
Here I go!
おい！おい！おい！おい！おい！おい！おい！おい！
Oi! Oi! Oi! Oi! Oi! Oi! Oi! Oi!
なんかズレてない？なんかズレてない？
Isn't something off? Isn't something out of sync?
ロボ子ちゃんズレてない？
Roboco-chan, aren't you out of sync?
アンポンタンステップ無理だよー。ごめんごめん。
The Anpontan Step is impossible! Sorry, sorry.
いや、でもなんかこの「アポタンシスターズ」で踊るの、めっちゃ久しぶりだね、ルーナ。
But dancing as the "Anpontan Sisters"... it's been such a long time, Luna.
そうだねー。ルーナさん、なんでこの2曲選択したの？
That's true. Luna, why did you choose these two songs?
えー、まずはね、この「バラライカ」。
Well, first, about "Baralaika"...
まず勝手言うと、アキローズ先輩を最初イメージして...
To put it simply, I first imagined Akirose-senpai...
えっ！それってもしかして... ウホウホ？
Eh! Does that mean... Uho uho?
ウホウホかなって。ウホウホ言ってる、なんかこれイメージしたら、アキローズ先輩...
I thought maybe "Uho uho". When I thought of the "Uho uho" part, I thought of Akirose-senpai...
ムキムキ先輩！
Buff senior!
拳（こぶし）の方や、それは。
That's the fist one!
なんだかピッタリなのらよねーと思ってこの曲選んじまったのらよ。
I thought it was a perfect fit, so I ended up choosing this song.
楽しすぎた！
It was so much fun!
うわー、合いの手言ってもらえばよかった。
Uwah, I should have had you do the interjections.
今度やるときはウホウホ言ってもらえばよかったのらね。うん。
Next time we do it, I'll have you do the "Uho uho". Yeah.
でもね、「バラライカ」、でもちょっとこれ歌ったら、最後はアイドルっぽい曲歌いたいなーと。
But after singing "Baralaika", I felt like ending with an idol-like song.
可愛さ補正したいしね。
To boost the cuteness, right?
それで、Baby Danceっしょね、3人で踊れたなら最高。
So with "Baby Dance", I thought it'd be great if the three of us could dance together.
凄かったね！3人で踊れてめっちゃ嬉しかった。
That was great! I was so happy we could dance as a trio.
だってさ、前にしたハロウィンの歌歌ったときさ、もうガッタガタだったじゃん。
I mean, remember when we sang that Halloween song before? It was a total mess.
あったねー。
That happened, didn't it?
成長したねー。
We've grown, haven't we?
成長したのらよー。3人ともめっちゃ成長したのらよ。
We have. The three of us have really grown.
そんな感じがするよ。
I feel that way too.
嬉しい、ありがとう。二人とも今日本当にありがとうね、来てくれて。
I'm happy, thank you. Thank you both so much for coming today.
おめでとう、ルーナ！おめでとう！
Congratulations, Luna! Congratulations!
ありがとう！この後も楽しんでね！
Thank you! Please enjoy the rest of the show too!
うん、頑張ってね！
Yeah, good luck!
バイバイー！ありがとうー！
Bye-bye! Thank you!
バイバイー！
Bye-bye!
行ってまいるのらー！バイバイー！
We're off now! Bye-bye!
行ってまいるのらよ。頑張るのら、ありがとう。
I'm off too. I'll do my best, thank you.
ああ、楽しかった。
Ah, that was fun.
でも、もっともっとみんなと歌いたいのらね。んー。
But I want to sing more and more with everyone.
んな！
Nna!
スバチョコに会いに行くのらー！
I'm going to see SubaChoko!
ほら、スバル、早く着替えないと間に合わないわよ。
Come on, Subaru, if you don't change quickly, you won't make it.
何に！？何に間に合わないの！？
To what!? What won't I make it to!?
チョコ先生が着替えさせたがるんだけど！怖い怖い怖い！いやいや、大丈夫、一人で着替えさせて！
Choco-sensei wants to force me to change! Scary, scary, scary! No, it's fine, let me change by myself!
ちょっと待ってー！ちょっと待ってー！
Wait a second! Wait a second!
ルーナも混ぜてー！
Let Luna join too!
混ざらねーよ！混ざらねー！
You're not joining! You're not!
混ぜて混ぜて！入れて！
Let me join, join! Let me in!
入れませんけど。ちょっとあの場所がここだとややこしいんで...
We won't let you in. Wait, it's confusing here...
場所転換します。場所転換します。
So let's change locations. Let's change locations.
ほら、ルーナ様センター立ちなさい、センター。
Come on, Luna-sama, stand in the center. In the center.
いひひ、いひひ。
Ehe-hehe, ehe-hehe.
今日も可愛いわね、ルーナ。
You're cute today too, Luna.
ありがとうのら。
Thank you.
どうしたの？どうしたの？
What's up? What's up?
え、今日は実はね、ルーナ2周年記念でね、ライブしてたのらやん。
Well, actually, today is my 2nd anniversary, and I was doing a live.
そうなんだ！おめでとう！
Oh, is that so! Congratulations!
ありがとうねー。
Thank you.
あ、じゃあ頑張ってね。え、ちょ、待って、ちょっと待って。
Ah, well then, good luck. Eh, wait, wait a second.
おい、ちょっと待て、お前ふざけんじゃねえ。
Hey, wait a minute, don't mess with me.
どうした、どうした？ルーナ様。
What's wrong, what's wrong, Luna-sama?
だからここに来たのは、せっかくならスバチョコルーナでね、歌って踊りたいと思って来たのらやん。
The reason I came here is that I thought I'd like for SubaChokoLuna to sing and dance together.
あらあらあら、しょうがないわね、もう。
Oh my, I guess we have no choice.
歌ってくれる？踊ってくれる？一緒に。
Will you sing? Will you dance? Together.
まあしょうがねえな、せっかくのルーナの頼みだからな。
Well, I guess we have no choice. Since it's Luna's request.
よし、じゃあ歌うのら！
Alright, then let's sing!
行くぞー！うおおおお！
Here we go! Waaaaaa!
うー！にゃー！
Uu! Nyaa!
世界はワー
The world is a whirl
はずみ！
of bouncing!
うー！にゃー！
Uu! Nyaa!
レッツニャー！
Let's nyaa!
心ぬるぬる異形の神々
Slime-covered hearts, bizarre gods
私もあなたも怖がりのものずき
Both you and I are timid but curious
形もろもろ異形と逃げれば
Various forms, if we flee with the bizarre
私とあなたは縁化で踊って
You and I, let's dance at the rim of the world
楽しいね、焼けるぞ溶けるぞ
It's fun, isn't it? We'll burn up, we'll melt down
生きものじゃない！
We aren't living things!
不黒冷え冷えそれでも好きです
Chilled to the bone, but I still like it
私がいちばん欲しいのは内緒よ
The thing I want most is a secret
姿ぱやぱやそれでは行きましょう
Our forms are hazy, so let's get going
私に満ちた淫らな不条理
An indecent absurdity fills me up
鏡には
In the mirror,
だ、だ、だれなの？
w-w-who is it?
映らない
It's not reflected.
だれなの？やだやだ
Who is it? No, no!
欲望は言葉にしなくちゃ
You have to put your desires into words
ほら
Look,
消えちゃうでしょう
they'll disappear otherwise
レッツニャー！
Let's nyaa!
太陽なんかまぶしくて
The sun is just so bright
(これは) 無限でドキドキ
(This is) an infinity of excitement
(ドキドキ!)
(Excitement!)
太陽バッカ眩しくて
The sun is just so bright
闇の方が素敵だよ
The darkness is even more wonderful
(素敵だよ!)
(Wonderful!)
(K-O! K-O!)
I wanna K-O!
燃えよ混沌無限大
Burn, chaos, to infinity
(ワクワク!)
(How exciting!)
(K-O! K-O!)
もらっせら K-O!
Mollasser K-O!
燃えるような気持ち
A burning feeling
(にゃっしー!)
(Nyassy!)
(うー! にゃー! うー! にゃー!)
(U-! Nya-! U-! Nya-!)
世界は
The world is...
(霞!)
(Haze!)
(うー! にゃー! うー! にゃー!) (Let's にゃ!)
(U-! Nya-! U-! Nya-!) (Let's nya!)
マジメな僕ボク 無謀な神カミ
Serious me-me, reckless god-god
私とあなたと 目的は違うの
You and I have different goals
キズナはムカムカ 無理やりされがち
Bonds are annoying, often forced upon us
私があなたを守るけどおピンチ
I'll protect you, but we're in a pinch
おかしいな 逃げるぞ
How strange, I'm gonna run
めっくそう!
Dammit!
(現代は行ってルー!)
(I'm going to modern times!)
ゴバリゴリゴリ ここまで来ました
Grinding along, I've come this far
私は騙せて 先を激ヤツ
I'm being fooled, the future is super hot
ホムラメラメラ ここではやめてと
The flames are flickering, don't do it here
私に黙って スカウトはしないで
Don't scout me without my permission
望むなら
If you wish
(K-O! K-O!) しましょうね
(K-O! K-O!) Let's do it
(出来んのだよ! やれやれ!)
(It can't be done! Good grief!)
願わくば 後形もなくね
I wish there's no trace left
(うー!)
(U-!)
(にゃー!)
(Nya-!)
(あなた...)
(You...)
(Let's にゃ!) 限界なんて 危険だった
(Let's nya!) The limit was dangerous
光もっとください
Give me more light
(ピカピカ!)
(Sparkle sparkle!)
限界なんて 危険だった
The limit was dangerous
光もって 刺激的!
More light, more stimulus!
(にゃっしー!)
(Nyassy!)
Madness madness!
You wanna madness!
呼べば混沌 駆け出して
If you call, chaos will come running
(ドキドキ!)
(Excitement!)
Madness madness!
I knew it madness!
呼べばきっと おしまい!
If you call, it'll surely be the end!
(にゃっしー!)
(Nyassy!)
(這い寄る!)
(Creeping!)
(混沌!)
(Chaos!)
(ニャルラトホップ!)
(Nyarlathotep!)
(うー! にゃー! うー! にゃー! うー! にゃー! うー! にゃー!) (Let's にゃ!)
(U-! Nya-! U-! Nya-! U-! Nya-! U-! Nya-!) (Let's nya!)
太陽なんか眩しくて 闇の方が無限大
The sun is so bright, the darkness is infinite
(ドキドキ!)
(Excitement!)
太陽バッカ眩しくて 闇の方が素敵だよ
The sun is just so bright, the darkness is wonderful
(素敵だよ!)
(Wonderful!)
(K-O! K-O!)
I wanna K-O!
燃えよ混沌無限大
Burn, chaos, to infinity
(ワクワク!)
(How exciting!)
(K-O! K-O!)
もらっせら K-O!
Mollasser K-O!
燃えるような気持ち
A burning feeling
(にゃっしー!)
(Nyassy!)
(這い寄る!)
(Creeping!)
(混沌!)
(Chaos!)
(ニャルラトホップ!)
(Nyarlathotep!)
ふぅー…あぁー、踊ったー!
Phew... Ah, we danced!
スバルも大丈夫ー?
Is Subaru okay too?
おう! 全然!
Yeah! Totally!
全然余裕なんだぜ!
I'm totally fine!
全然元気だぜー!
I'm totally energetic!
わぁー、嬉しいよー! 3人で踊れたぜー!
Wow, I'm happy! We could dance as a trio!
いえーい! いえーい! ありよよーん!
Yay! Yay! Thanks!
なんかこの間も踊った気がするけどね!
I feel like we danced just the other day too though!
熱、ルーナおめでとう!
Hot, Luna, congratulations!
ありがと、ありがとねー!
Thank you, thank you!
また3人で踊れて、すごいルーナ嬉しい、嬉しい、ありがとねー!
Dancing as a trio again makes Luna so happy, so happy, thank you!
よかったよー、満足した?
That's good, are you satisfied?
満足してない!
I'm not satisfied!
まだ、まだまだまだまだよー!
Not yet, not yet yet yet yet!
まぁ、まだまだなのよー。
Well, there's still more.
欲張りさんなんだからー。
Such a greedy person.
次はね、あの、今ね、スバチョコルーナで踊ったってことは次は…
Next, well, since we danced as SubaChocoLuna, then next...
おと?
Oh?
スバチョコルーナたん! でね、
SubaChocoLunaTan!
一緒に歌って踊りたいのらー!
I want to sing and dance together!
いいね! 踊りたいぜ! いいよ!
Sounds good! I want to dance! Okay!
だからこのあと、ぼたんちゃん呼びに行くのらー!
So I'm going to call Botan-chan now!
おっけー、行くのらー!
Okay, let's go!
いぇーい! 行くぞ行くぞ行くぞー!
Yay! Let's go let's go let's go!
ぼたんちゃん! ぼたんちゃん! お待たせー!
Botan-chan! Botan-chan! Sorry to keep you waiting!
まだまだ待たせてもないよー。来たよ来たよー。
I haven't even been waiting long. You're here, you're here.
来たよ来たよー。
We're here, we're here.
え、今日なになに? 何すんの?
Eh, what's happening today? What are we doing?
え、今日実はね、ルーナ2周年記念ライブしてるのらよー!
Eh, actually today Luna is doing her 2nd anniversary live!
おめでとー! 一人ずつ仲間集めてるんだ、今。
Congratulations! I'm gathering teammates one by one now.
あ、マジ?
Ah, really?
そう! 今メンバー揃ったのらよー!
Yeah! Now the members are all here!
おー、魔王倒しに行く感じ?
Oh, like going to defeat the demon king?
行く行く行く! 一緒に倒しに行くのらー!
Let's go go go! We're going to defeat him together!
行くぞ行くぞ行くぞー!
Let's go let's go let's go!
じゃあ、みんなフォーメーション展開なのらー!
Then, everyone, deploy formation!
何? フォーメーション?
What? Formation?
そうなの! みんな並んで、フォーメーション!
That's right! Everyone line up, formation!
シュシュシュシュシュ…!
Whoosh whoosh whoosh...!
シャキーン!
Cling!
行くわよ!
Here we go!
ポジョン!
Position!
Joyful!
君の声を聞かせて
Let me hear your voice
さあ 冒険してみない?
Now, why don't we go on an adventure?
楽しいこと始めよう
Let's start something fun
遊びたい! ぜったい! ぜったいたいたい!
Want to play! Definitely! Definitely, definitely!
I wanna Joy! to Joy! to Joy!
Pop na Baby!
Joy! to Joy! to Joy!
Happy na People!
余所見なんかじゃない
I'm not looking away
自信ありげなピースサイン
A confident peace sign
君の瞳にキスして
Kiss your eyes
笑いたい! ぜったい! ぜったいたいたい!
Want to laugh! Definitely! Definitely, definitely!
I wanna Joy! to Joy! to Joy!
Yokina Baby!
Joy! to Joy! to Joy!
Happy na Say-Yeah!
君の心はそう もっと DO! DO!
Your heart is, yeah, even more DO! DO!
僕の心もそう いっそ GOOD! GOOD!
My heart is also, rather, GOOD! GOOD!
弾けてるんじゃない? It's Joyful!
Isn't it bursting? It's Joyful!
ハピ・プ・ピ・ポ・パ・ブ・イェーイ!
Happy Pappy Bubble... Yeah!
Joy! to Joy! to Joy!
Pop na Baby!
Happy na People!
ドキドキしちゃうの なんでだろ
I wonder why my heart is pounding
ズキズキしちゃうの なんでだろ
I wonder why it's aching
この指にとまるのは
Perching on this finger
どんな運命なんだぜ 最短!
What kind of fate is it? Shortest!
誰もがだって 終わっちゃう
Because everyone eventually ends
Everybody いつか 終わっちゃう
Everybody, someday it'll end
いついつまでも この時を
Forever and ever, this moment
最終形はきっと 修正なしで
The final form will surely be without corrections
ハピ・プ・ピ・ポ・パ・ブ...
Happy Pappy Bubble...
ぜったい! ぜったいたいたい!
Definitely! Definitely, definitely!
I wanna Joy! to Joy! to Joy!
Yokina Baby!
Joy! to Joy! to Joy!
Happy na Say-Yeah!
君の心はそう もっと DO! DO!
Your heart is, yeah, even more DO! DO!
僕の心もそう いっそ GOOD! GOOD!
My heart is also, rather, GOOD! GOOD!
弾けてるんじゃない? It's Joyful!
Isn't it bursting? It's Joyful!
ハピ・プ・ピ・ポ・パ・ブ・イェーイ!
Happy Pappy Bubble... Yeah!
最後は、アイドルっぽく歌いたいのら！
Lastly, I want to sing like an idol!
せーの！
One, two!
Snow halation!
不思議だね 今の気持ち
It's strange, this feeling right now
空から降ってきたみたい
It's like it fell from the sky
特別な季節の色が
The colors of a special season
ときめきを見せるよ
Show me the excitement
初めて出会った時から
From the moment we first met
予感に騒ぐ心のメロディ
The melody of my heart stirring with premonition
とめられない 止まらない
Unstoppable, it won't stop
なぜ
Why
届けて 切なさには
Reach out, for this sadness
名前をつけようか Snow halation
Shall we give it a name? Snow halation
想いが重なるまで
Until our feelings overlap
待てずに 悔しいけど好きって純情
I can't wait, it's frustrating but it's pure love
微熱の中 躊躇ってもダメだね
Even if I hesitate in this slight fever, it's no good
飛び込む勇気に賛成
I agree with the courage to dive in
まもなく Start!!
Starting soon!!
Snow halation
音もなく気配もなく
Without a sound or a sign,
静かに運命は変わる
Fate changes quietly.
これからの未来に胸の
Looking towards the future, my heart's...
鼓動が早くなる
...beat speeds up.
例えば困った時には
For example, when in trouble...
すぐ駆けつけて抱きしめたくて
...I want to rush over and hold you.
どこにいてもどこでも
Wherever you are, no matter where...
はい！はい！
High! High!
急いでいつのまにか
...hurrying before I knew it.
大きくなりすぎたエモーション
This emotion that has grown too large.
夢だけ見てるようじゃ
Just dreaming is...
辛いよ　恋人は君と言いたい
...painful; I want to call you my lover.
優しい目が戸惑ってる嫌だよ
Your kind eyes are wavering, I hate it.
このまま一気に愛情
Just like this, all at once, my love...
あずけて Please!!
...entrust it to you, please!!
届けて切なさには
Deliver it, to this heartache...
名前をつけようか Snow halation
...shall we give it a name? Snow halation.
想いが重なるまで
Until our feelings overlap...
待てずに悔しいけど好きって純情
...I can't wait, it's frustrating, but this love is pure.
微熱の中ためらってもダメダメ
Even if I hesitate in this slight fever, it's no good.
飛び込む勇気に賛成
I'm all for the courage to dive in.
まもなく Start!!
Starting soon!!
わー！よかったー！
Wow! That was great!
ねー、よかったねー
Yeah, it was really good.
ルーナおめでとう！
Congratulations, Luna!
ありがとなのらー
Thank you nanora.
ちょこ先生、おーたんちゃん、スバルちゃん、今日はいてくれてありがとう
Choco-sensei, Botan-chan, Subaru-chan, thank you for being here today.
こちらこそありがとう！
Thank you as well!
呼んでくれてありがとう。
Thanks for inviting us.
おめでとう。
Congratulations.
じゃあルーナ、最後まで頑張ってな！
Well then Luna, do your best until the end!
頑張ってねー！
Good luck!
うん、頑張るのらー！
Yeah, I'll do my best nanora!
頑張れー！バイバーイ！
Good luck! Bye-bye!
ありがとなのらー！
Thank you nanora!
おめでとうー！バイバーイ！
Congrats! Bye-bye!
ありがとなのらー。
Thank you nanora.
みんな、ありがとう。
Everyone, thank you.
ルーナが今ここを迎えられたのは、ルーナイトを始めとしたみんなのおかげなのら。
The reason Luna could reach this point is thanks to everyone, especially the LuKnights.
次はこの歌を歌います。
Next, I'll sing this song.
好きになって！もっと私を見て！もっと！
Fall in love with me! Look at me more! More!
ファンサ
Fansa
恩返しは愛のこもった投げキッスで
I'll repay you with a blow kiss full of love...
運命じゃない！？目が合ってるよ
Isn't it fate!? Our eyes are meeting.
ハート作って恋しちゃってください！
Make a heart and please fall in love!
やれることなんでもしますNG無しで
I'll do everything I can. No taboos...
体当たり挑戦！
...taking on any challenge!
エゴサで見つけたアンチのコメ
I found anti comments through ego-searching,
お前らなんなのより分かってるし
I understand them better than 'who are you guys?'
でも大丈夫ここに立てばみんながいる
But it's okay, if I stand here, everyone is with me.
いくよ！
Here we go!
好きになって！もっと私を見て！もっと！
Fall in love with me! Look at me more! More!
恩返しは愛のこもった投げキッスで
I'll repay you with a blow kiss full of love...
虜にする！もっと！
I'll captivate you! More!
もっと楽しんでて
Enjoy it even more
愛のこもったスペシャルなナイト
A special night filled with love
ファンサしちゃうぞ
I'll give you fan service!
お手紙も書いてください
Please write letters too
何度も読んで宝物にします
I'll read them many times and make them my treasure
スキャンダルはまだ早いけど
It's too early for a scandal, but
裏切り待ってません
I'm not waiting for a betrayal
宣言しときまーす
I'm declaring it now
ひどい嫌がらせには負けない
I won't lose to terrible harassment
ぶっちぎりの実力で勝ってやる
I'll win with overwhelming skill
そこら負けない負けず嫌い
I'm a sore loser who won't lose to anyone
私はいる
I'm here
行くよ！
Let's go!
拳上げて
Raise your fists
もっと汗をかいて
Sweat even more
もっと恩返しは 愛のこもったルナのビームで
Repaying you even more with Luna's beam filled with love
大胆不敵
Fearless
もっとまだまだだね
More, not yet enough
もっと歌わせてね
Let me sing even more
愛のこもったわがままソング
A selfish song filled with love
ファンサしちゃうぞ
I'll give you fan service!
あー 終わりが近づく
Ah, the end is approaching
寂しいな
It's so lonely
楽しいのに泣きそうだよ
It's fun, but I'm about to cry
次も次もまた会えるよね
We can meet again and again, right?
また会えるよね
We can meet again, right?
約束！
Promise!
皆さんに溢れている言葉も 心無い誰かの言葉さえも
The words overflowing from everyone, and even heartless words from someone...
必要なんだ 必要なんだ
...are all necessary, they're necessary
強くなろう
Let's become strong
次は叫んで
Next, scream
もっと楽しんじゃえ
Enjoy it even more
もっと忘れないで
Don't forget even more
特別な日になりますように
I hope it becomes a special day
共に歌う
Singing together
ずっと共に歩む
Walking together forever
ずっと合言葉は とびきりの L-O-V-E
The password forever is the ultimate L-O-V-E
好きになって
Fall in love with me
もっと私を見て
Look at me even more
もっと恩返しは 愛のこもった投げキッスで
Repaying you even more with a blown kiss filled with love
虜にするよ
I'll captivate you
もっと夢を見せる
I'll show you even more dreams
もっと楽しんでて
Enjoy it even more
愛のこもったスペシャルなナイト
A special night filled with love
ファンサしちゃうぞ
I'll give you fan service!
ずっと応援してくれてるみんなへの感謝、どうだったのらこな？
My gratitude to everyone who's been supporting me... How was it?
みんな泣いてんのか？
Is everyone crying?
ルーナは泣いてねえぞ、ルーナは泣いてねえのらこな。
Luna's not crying. Luna's not crying, you know?
みんなすぐ泣くからな。ルーナイトすぐ泣く。
Everyone cries so easily. LuKnights cry right away.
ほら、泣いたすぐ泣いた。
See? You cried, you cried right away.
ルーナは泣いてねえのらこな。
Luna's not crying, you know?
みんな... よかった、本当。
Everyone... I'm glad, really.
泣いてる... 泣き虫姫。最高だった、本当。
Crying... crybaby princess. It was the best, really.
ありがとう、みんな聴いてくれて。
Thank you, everyone, for listening.
胸がいっぱいなのらよ。
My heart is so full.
でも、ここからは2周年記念グッズの方を紹介していきたいと思うのら。
But, from here I want to introduce the 2nd anniversary goods.
みんな落ち着いて。
Everyone, calm down.
見て！みんなみんな。
Look! Everyone, everyone.
可愛いでしょ？
It's cute, right?
姫森ルーナ2周年記念グッズ、こちら全部で4種あります。
There are 4 types of Himemori Luna 2nd anniversary goods in total.
早速見ていくのらよ。
Let's take a look right away.
じゃん！
Ta-da!
まずは、かんざきパパ描き下ろしのラバーマットです！
First, a rubber mat newly drawn by Kanzaki Papa!
ドレス姿のルーナと新衣装のワンピースのルーナが対になった可愛いイラストなのらよ。
It's a cute illustration with Luna in her dress and Luna in her new one-piece dress paired up.
10月にルーナ誕生日記念グッズとして出した...
Released in October as Luna's birthday commemorative goods...
...パッドとかもあるでしょ？
...PAD and such, right?
あれに合わせて、デスク周りをね、充実させようとラバーマットにしたのらよ。
To match that, I decided to make a rubber mat to spruce up the area around your desk, nora.
そして次こちら！
And next is this!
宝崎シイナ先生描き下ろしの、BIGなメガネ置きアクリルスタンド！
A BIG glasses stand acrylic stand, drawn by Housaki Shiina-sensei!
こちらはね、全高40cmもあるね、大きいサイズのメガネ置きスタンドなのらよ。
This is a large-sized glasses stand, about 40cm in height, nora.
メガネでもサングラスでもね、ルナもサングラスするからね。
Whether it's glasses or sunglasses... Luna wears sunglasses too, you know.
好きなものをルナにね、こう着けてほしいのら。
I want you to put your favorite things on Luna like this, nora.
そして次、パパ描き下ろしラバーマットと同じイラストで、クリーナークロスもあるのら。
And next, with the same illustration as Papa's rubber mat, there's also a cleaner cloth, nora.
さっきのBIGメガネ置きアクリルスタンド、メガネってね、こちら大きめのサイズになってるからメガネ拭きにも使えるし、
The BIG glasses stand from earlier... this is a bit large, so it can be used for cleaning glasses,
パソコンとか、パッドとか、窓拭きにも使える一品になっているのらよ。
and it's a useful item for cleaning computers, PADs, or even windows, nora.
そして次、ルーナイト紋章ピンバッジ！
And next, the Lunight Crest Pin Badge!
ルナモチーフがふんだんに盛り込まれた素敵なデザインになっているのら。
It's a lovely design with plenty of Luna motifs, nora.
こちらもね、10月の誕生日記念グッズとして出したマグカップと同じデザインになってるのら。可愛い！
This also has the same design as the mug released for the October birthday, nora. Cute!
ピンバッジはね、このピンクのね、可愛い箱に入れて、みんなにお届けします！
The pin badge will be delivered in this cute pink box!
そしてそして！こちらフルセット購入の方限定で、ポストカードとボイスの特典があります！
And, and! This is a bonus for those who purchase the full set: a postcard and voice bonus!
数量限定で、直筆サインとメッセージ入りのポストカード＋特典ボイスが付いてくるのらよ。
In limited quantities, a handwritten signature and postcard with a message, plus a bonus voice will be included, nora.
特典ボイスには、ルナの今までの思いとか色んなお話を収録してあるので、ぜひ聴いてほしいのら。
The bonus voice includes Luna's feelings until now and various stories, so please do listen to it, nora.
そして最後、重大発表なのら！
And finally, a major announcement, nora!
長らく、ついにお披露目します！
After a long time, I'm finally unveiling it!
みんな、いっぱい待たせてしまって、ごめんならね。
Sorry for making everyone wait so long, nora.
こちらね、1月中にはダウンロード配信できる予定で、ジャケットイラストもね、かんざきパパに描いてもらっているので、また分かり次第みんなに告知するのらね。
This is scheduled for download distribution in January, and Kanzaki Papa is drawing the jacket illustration, so I'll let you know as soon as it's ready, nora.
楽しみに待っててほしいのら。
Please look forward to it, nora.
姫森ルナ活動2周年。ルーナイトたち、これからもルナのそばにいてください。
Himemori Luna's 2nd anniversary. Lunights, please stay by Luna's side from now on as well.
それでは歌います！Cパートもあるので、最後までぜひぜひ見てください。
Well then, I'll sing! There's also a C-part, so please watch until the very end.
絶対忠誠なのらななのらー！
Absolute Loyalty nora nano nanora!
んなああああ
Nnaaaaa!
みんなおりゅ〜？(・o・)
Is everyone here? (・o・)
なのなのら！
Nano nanora!
絶対忠誠♡なのなのら！
Absolute Loyalty ♡ Nano Nanora!
お菓子の国のお姫様
The princess of Candy Kingdom
とびきりプリティーな0歳児
With a super pretty 0-year-old suffix
ピアノだって弾けるんだし
I can even play the piano
赤ちゃんじゃないのらよ！
I'm not a baby, you know!
ワガママだって言うけれど
You say I'm selfish, but...
ルーナはお姫様なのらから
Luna is a princess, after all
ルーナイトたちも執事も
Lunights and stewards too...
いちいちうるさいのら！
...are so noisy every time, nora!
さあルーナイトたち準備はできたのら〜？
Now, Lunights, are you ready?
出陣なのら〜！
Let's head out!
パフェもしゅわしゅわも
Parfaits and fizzy drinks too
早く用意するのら！
Hurry up and prepare them, na-no-ra!
あれもこれも食べたいのら！
I want to eat this and that, na-no-ra!
おいしいのはひとりじめ♪
The delicious ones are all for me♪
まずいのや苦いのは
The bad or bitter ones
ルーナイト達に差し入れ！
Are gifts for the LuKnights!
チョコレートの噴水も
Chocolate fountains too
キャンディの首飾りも
Candy necklaces too
素敵なのかたくさんあるのら
There are so many wonderful things, na-no-ra
だからルーナのために集めてきてね♡
So collect them for Luna, okay?♡
絶対絶対絶対約束
Absolute, absolute, absolute promise
なのなのら！
Na-no-na-no-ra!
お料理だってお手のもの☆
Cooking is a specialty of mine☆
みんなのハートも焦がすのらよ♡
I'll scorch everyone's hearts too, na-no-ra♡
ナノリッシュだってパーフェクト☆
Nanolish is perfect too☆
“すぺしゃる”なじーにあす！
A "special" genius!
ゲームするのも好きだけど
I like playing games, but
怖いのは絶対イヤなのら……
I absolutely hate scary things, na-no-ra......
笑ったそこのルーナイト！
You LuKnight over there who laughed!
後でお仕置きなのら♡
I'll punish you later, na-no-ra♡
毎日楽しくて
Every day is fun
みんなで踊って　今日もまた大騒ぎ！
Dancing together, another uproar today!
あれもこれも遊ぶのら！
I'll play with this and that, na-no-ra!
楽しいのはひとりじめ♪
The fun ones are all for me♪
怖いのや痛いのは
The scary or painful ones
ルーナイト達にお任せ！
I'll leave those to the LuKnights!
お月様のブランコも
The moon swing too
流れ星スライダーも
The shooting star slider too
楽しいのたくさんあるのら
There are so many fun things, na-no-ra
だから
So
全然遊び足りてないのら！
I haven't played nearly enough, na-no-ra!
まだまだまだまだまだまだ追随
I'm still, still, still, still following along
なのなのら！
Na-no-na-no-ra!
んなぁぁぁぁぁ
Nnaaaaaaaa
ルーナの事ワガママワガママって
Calling Luna selfish, selfish
いちいちうるさいのらね～！
You're so annoying!~!
ルーナは好きじゃない人にワガママは言わないのらよ！
Luna doesn't act selfishly towards people she doesn't like!
それだけルーナイトの事頼りにしてるってことなのら
It means I'm relying on the LuKnights that much
だから…これからも先もルーナの事、
So... from now on too,
守ってくれるのらよね？
you'll keep protecting Luna, right?
ほらね、着いてきて！
See, come along!
ルーナのナイトさま♡
Luna's dear knights♡
んーでね♪
And then...♪
あれもこれも欲しいのら！
I want this and that, na-no-ra!
全部全部欲しいのら！
I want everything, everything, na-no-ra!
ルーナとルーナイトで
With Luna and the LuKnights
たこ焼きパーティーするのら！
Let's have a takoyaki party, na-no-ra!
もっともっと楽しい事！
More and more fun things!
ずっとずっと嬉しい事！
Always and forever happy things!
一緒に作っていけたらね
I hope we can make them together
きっとルーナとみんなの物語は
Surely the story of Luna and everyone
おとぎ話になっちゃうのかも！
Might turn into a fairy tale!
プリンセスの願いかなえて♡
Grant the princess's wish♡
絶対絶対絶対忠誠♡
Absolute, absolute, absolute loyalty♡
なのなのら！
Na-no-na-no-ra!
ルーナイトへ♡
To LuKnights♡
早かったような、短かったような…あっという間の2年間だったのらね。
It felt fast, or maybe it was short... these 2 years passed in an instant, na-no-ra.
ルーナイトはどう感じた？？
How did the LuKnights feel??
いつもそばに居てくれて本当にありがちゅ～！！
Thank you so much for always being by my side~!!
これからもルーナと一緒に前に進んでいこうね！！
Let's keep moving forward together with Luna from now on too!!
大好き♡
I love you♡
姫森ルーナなのら♡
It's Himemori Luna, na-no-ra♡
ルーナイトへ♡
To Lu-Knights ♡
早かったような、短かったような･･･
あっという間の2年間だったのらね。
It felt fast, or maybe short...
these 2 years went by in the blink of an eye.
ルーナイトはどう感じたのら？
How did you feel, Lu-Knights?
いつもそばに居てくれて本当にありがとうなのら〜！！
Thank you so much for always being by my side!!
これからもルーナと一緒に前に進んでいこうね！！
Let's keep moving forward together with Luna!!
大好き♡ るなより♡
I love you ♡ From Luna ♡
姫森ルーナ 2周年記念
2nd Anniversary Live 2022
Himemori Luna 2nd Anniversary